Jasmine Floyd

I'm passionate about solving users' problems and building products that improve the experiences of the people who use them. My background includes launching new products, enhancing user engagement, and driving growth through strategic planning and stakeholder alignment. With a strong focus on collaboration and innovation, I love turning complex challenges into opportunities while helping teams achieve their full potential in delivering exceptional outcomes for customers.

Atlanta, GA (973) 573-9356 jasmine.floyd86@gmail.com LinkedIn Profile Portfolio Website

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Popmenu | Senior Product Manager

OCT 2021 - PRESENT

- Drive the product strategy and roadmap for customer acquisition and retention, focusing on Restaurant Operations and Guest Communications.
- Recent cross-functional initiatives include collaborating with Client Success and Marketing to build a targeted push notification strategy leveraging key data points and AI technology which has increased user engagement by 35%.
- Leverage data analytics and qualitative user feedback to deliver innovative solutions that support our strategic business goals and increase the value and ROI for our users.

Upside Business Travel | Senior Product Manager

JUN 2020 - AUG 2021

- Led the product vision and planning for Upside Business Travel, focusing on e-comm
 Checkout Process and Travel Manager tools.
- Led the strategic pivot during the pandemic with creating Upside Financial, a 0-1
 product and business launched that enabled over 800+ businesses to secure PPP
 funds, with over 95% achieving loan forgiveness.

Reliant Technology | Senior Product Manager

MAY 2017 - MAR 2020

- Conducted extensive user research to prioritize customer needs, ensuring product development aligned with user expectations.
- Provided technical leadership for deployment of internal tools (Salesforce, JIRA), led training, and managed product/app releases, improving engineering management practices.

AvePoint | Product Manager, SaaS

JAN 2013 - May 2017

- Led the international product team across development, QA testing, and user experience disciplines, focusing primarily on cloud applications.
- Oversaw the entire product lifecycle, championing user-centered design and aligning product development with user needs and business goals.

SKILLS

Outcome-based Strategic Planning and Roadmap Development

Developing 0-1 Products in a startup environment

Empowering product teams with a strong data culture

Proficient in JIRA, Shortcut, Looker, Snowflake, Tableau, Figma, InVision, HTML/CSS, Javascript, React

CERTIFICATIONS

Pragmatic PMC-V
Pragmatic Marketing - 2019

Advanced product management strategies focused on market-driven principles.

Certified PM

AIPMM - 2021

Comprehensive training, covering the full lifecycle from ideation to market success.

SLII Leadership

Blanchard Management - 2023

Situational leadership expertise, enabling adaptive management to maximize team performance and development.

EDUCATION

Johnson C. Smith University, Charlotte, NC - B.S.

Graduated with a Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Science - Information Technology, minor in Business Finance.